[
  {
    "id": 4401,
    "question": "entrevistas",
    "questionDetails": "Hoy tenemos nuestras entrevistas.",
    "answer": "interviews",
    "answerDetails": "We have our interviews today."
  },
  {
    "id": 4402,
    "question": "pusiera",
    "questionDetails": "Le dije que pusiera.",
    "answer": "put",
    "answerDetails": "I told him to put."
  },
  {
    "id": 4403,
    "question": "conociera",
    "questionDetails": "Con cualquiera que conociera su rutina.",
    "answer": "knew",
    "answerDetails": "Anyone who knew his itinerary."
  },
  {
    "id": 4404,
    "question": "sordo",
    "questionDetails": "Escuché un golpe sordo en la habitación de arriba.",
    "answer": "dull, muffled",
    "answerDetails": "I heard a dull thud in the room upstairs."
  },
  {
    "id": 4405,
    "question": "abuelos",
    "questionDetails": "El tiene cuatro abuelos vivos.",
    "answer": "grandparents",
    "answerDetails": "He got four living grandparents."
  },
  {
    "id": 4406,
    "question": "usó",
    "questionDetails": "Usó a tu amigo como un manantial de tinta.",
    "answer": "used, wore",
    "answerDetails": "Used to your friend as a source of ink."
  },
  {
    "id": 4407,
    "question": "líneas",
    "questionDetails": "Las líneas de voltaje han caído.",
    "answer": "lines",
    "answerDetails": "The power lines are down."
  },
  {
    "id": 4408,
    "question": "robé",
    "questionDetails": "Yo robé una cuchara.",
    "answer": "stole, swiped, robbed",
    "answerDetails": "I stole a spoon."
  },
  {
    "id": 4409,
    "question": "soñar",
    "questionDetails": "Se acabó el soñar.",
    "answer": "dream, daydream",
    "answerDetails": "The dream is over!"
  },
  {
    "id": 4410,
    "question": "policial",
    "questionDetails": "Tú tenías información policial desde dentro.",
    "answer": "police",
    "answerDetails": "You had inside police information."
  },
  {
    "id": 4411,
    "question": "próximos",
    "answer": "Next"
  },
  {
    "id": 4412,
    "question": "recibimos",
    "answer": "we got"
  },
  {
    "id": 4413,
    "question": "actividad",
    "questionDetails": "El único signo de la actividad humana ahora es la carga de barcos de los excurdores de día de la península.",
    "answer": "activity",
    "answerDetails": "The only sign of human activity now is the boatload of day trippers from the mainland."
  },
  {
    "id": 4414,
    "question": "documentación",
    "questionDetails": "Usted tendrá que completar la documentación pertinente.",
    "answer": "documentation, identification",
    "answerDetails": "You will have to complete the relevant documentation."
  },
  {
    "id": 4415,
    "question": "usado",
    "questionDetails": "Mi bañador estaba muy usado y, por eso, me he comprado uno nuevo.",
    "answer": "worn",
    "answerDetails": "My swimming suit was really worn, so I bought a new one."
  },
  {
    "id": 4416,
    "question": "asustando",
    "questionDetails": "Estás asustando a los chicos.",
    "answer": "scaring, frightening, freaking out",
    "answerDetails": "You are scaring the kids."
  },
  {
    "id": 4417,
    "question": "estarían",
    "answer": "they would be"
  },
  {
    "id": 4418,
    "question": "dejaré",
    "questionDetails": "Te dejaré las llaves en la mesa.",
    "answer": "i will leave",
    "answerDetails": "I will leave the keys on the table for you."
  },
  {
    "id": 4419,
    "question": "quema",
    "questionDetails": "Algunos piensan que se debería gravar con un impuesto la quema de combustibles fósiles.",
    "answer": "burning",
    "answerDetails": "Some people think there should be a tax on the burning of fossil fuels."
  },
  {
    "id": 4420,
    "question": "solucionado",
    "questionDetails": "Me encantaría saber qué lo ha solucionado.",
    "answer": "solved, fixed, resolved",
    "answerDetails": "I shall be happy to hear you have solved it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4421,
    "question": "nerviosos",
    "questionDetails": "Los jefes están nerviosos.",
    "answer": "nervous, nerve, jumpy",
    "answerDetails": "The brass is nervous."
  },
  {
    "id": 4422,
    "question": "eligió",
    "answer": "he chose"
  },
  {
    "id": 4423,
    "question": "mientes",
    "questionDetails": "Sé que no me mientes.",
    "answer": "lie, liar",
    "answerDetails": "I know you never lie to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 4424,
    "question": "quemado",
    "questionDetails": "No había más que pasto quemado aquí.",
    "answer": "burnt",
    "answerDetails": "There was nothing here but burnt grass."
  },
  {
    "id": 4425,
    "question": "dedicas",
    "questionDetails": "Y tu a que te dedicas?",
    "answer": "dedicate yourself, do",
    "answerDetails": "And you’re a that you dedicate yourself?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4426,
    "question": "miento",
    "questionDetails": "Yo no miento a usted.",
    "answer": "lie, ment",
    "answerDetails": "I no lie to you."
  },
  {
    "id": 4427,
    "question": "esfuerzos",
    "questionDetails": "A pesar de todos nuestros esfuerzos, no conseguimos nuestra meta.",
    "answer": "striving",
    "answerDetails": "Despite all our striving, we failed to meet our goal."
  },
  {
    "id": 4428,
    "question": "veíamos",
    "questionDetails": "Hacía tiempo que no nos veíamos.",
    "answer": "saw",
    "answerDetails": "There was a time that we saw."
  },
  {
    "id": 4429,
    "question": "apartamento",
    "questionDetails": "Usted tiene un bonito apartamento.",
    "answer": "apartment",
    "answerDetails": "You have a nice apartment."
  },
  {
    "id": 4430,
    "question": "créame",
    "answer": "trust me"
  },
  {
    "id": 4431,
    "question": "david",
    "answer": "David, Dave"
  },
  {
    "id": 4432,
    "question": "ayúdeme",
    "questionDetails": "Scully, ayúdeme a retirar la piel.",
    "answer": "help",
    "answerDetails": "Scully, help remove the skin."
  },
  {
    "id": 4433,
    "question": "ubicación",
    "questionDetails": "La ubicación del hotel es ideal.",
    "answer": "location",
    "answerDetails": "The hotel has an ideal location."
  },
  {
    "id": 4434,
    "question": "sánchez",
    "answer": "Sanchez"
  },
  {
    "id": 4435,
    "question": "chofer",
    "questionDetails": "Mi chofer no vino esta mañana.",
    "answer": "chauffeur",
    "answerDetails": "My chauffeur didn’t show up this morning."
  },
  {
    "id": 4436,
    "question": "conteste",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo conteste las preguntas.",
    "answer": "answer",
    "answerDetails": "Just answer the questions."
  },
  {
    "id": 4437,
    "question": "señoritas",
    "questionDetails": "Señoritas quiero que conozcan a unos invitados muy especiales.",
    "answer": "ladies, young ladies, senoritas",
    "answerDetails": "I want you to know ladies some very special guests."
  },
  {
    "id": 4438,
    "question": "súbete",
    "questionDetails": "Súbete a la cama.",
    "answer": "get",
    "answerDetails": "Get on the bed."
  },
  {
    "id": 4439,
    "question": "desaparición",
    "questionDetails": "La desaparición de la industria.",
    "answer": "demise, disappearance",
    "answerDetails": "The demise of industry."
  },
  {
    "id": 4440,
    "question": "vecina",
    "questionDetails": "Una vecina me ofrece dar una vuelta.",
    "answer": "neighbor, neighbouring, nearby",
    "answerDetails": "A neighbor offered me a ride."
  },
  {
    "id": 4441,
    "question": "escoger",
    "questionDetails": "Te toca a ti escoger.",
    "answer": "pick",
    "answerDetails": "It’s your turn to pick."
  },
  {
    "id": 4442,
    "question": "tigre",
    "questionDetails": "Como para hacer el salto del tigre.",
    "answer": "tiger",
    "answerDetails": "How to make the jump tiger."
  },
  {
    "id": 4443,
    "question": "martínez",
    "answer": "Martinez"
  },
  {
    "id": 4444,
    "question": "acostar",
    "questionDetails": "Se fue a acostar molesto.",
    "answer": "bed, lie down",
    "answerDetails": "He went to bed upset."
  },
  {
    "id": 4445,
    "question": "perrito",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que sea un perrito.",
    "answer": "puppy",
    "answerDetails": "I hope it’s a puppy."
  },
  {
    "id": 4446,
    "question": "interesada",
    "answer": "Interested"
  },
  {
    "id": 4447,
    "question": "vuestra",
    "questionDetails": "Ya sabéis lo que opina vuestra madre.",
    "answer": "your",
    "answerDetails": "You know how your mother feels about that."
  },
  {
    "id": 4448,
    "question": "matamos",
    "questionDetails": "Todos a los que matamos.",
    "answer": "kill",
    "answerDetails": "All of those we kill."
  },
  {
    "id": 4449,
    "question": "pensión",
    "questionDetails": "Jackie tiene una pensión completa en el dormitorio de la universidad.",
    "answer": "pension",
    "answerDetails": "Jackie has full pension at the University’s dormitory."
  },
  {
    "id": 4450,
    "question": "cuentos",
    "questionDetails": "Los cuentos tienen todos la misma estructura.",
    "answer": "tales, stories, short stories",
    "answerDetails": "Tales all have the same structure."
  },
  {
    "id": 4451,
    "question": "invento",
    "questionDetails": "Envía fotografías, diagramas y descripciones de tu invento.",
    "answer": "invention, invented, figment",
    "answerDetails": "Submit pictures, diagrams, and descriptions of your invention."
  },
  {
    "id": 4452,
    "question": "viví",
    "questionDetails": "Una vez viví aquí.",
    "answer": "lived",
    "answerDetails": "I once lived here."
  },
  {
    "id": 4453,
    "question": "noto",
    "answer": "Noto"
  },
  {
    "id": 4454,
    "question": "déjelo",
    "questionDetails": "Si la está maltratando, déjelo, Sra. Vázquez.",
    "answer": "leave him",
    "answerDetails": "If he’s abusing you, leave him, Mrs. Vazquez."
  },
  {
    "id": 4455,
    "question": "bendita",
    "questionDetails": "Bendita tú entre las mujeres.",
    "answer": "blessed, holy, bless",
    "answerDetails": "Blessed are you among women."
  },
  {
    "id": 4456,
    "question": "háblame",
    "questionDetails": "Ahora háblame de todos esos aviones …",
    "answer": "tell me",
    "answerDetails": "Now just tell me what all those planes …"
  },
  {
    "id": 4457,
    "question": "artículo",
    "questionDetails": "Leí un artículo interesante sobre la crisis económica en el periódico.",
    "answer": "article",
    "answerDetails": "I read an interesting article about the economic crisis in the newspaper."
  },
  {
    "id": 4458,
    "question": "orejas",
    "questionDetails": "Hubo un tiempo en las orejas fueron cortadas.",
    "answer": "ears",
    "answerDetails": "Time was when your ears were clipped."
  },
  {
    "id": 4459,
    "question": "prometes",
    "questionDetails": "Si me prometes que será solo una vez.",
    "answer": "promise",
    "answerDetails": "If you promise it’ll just be this one time."
  },
  {
    "id": 4460,
    "question": "garantía",
    "questionDetails": "El banco retiene el título de propiedad del coche como garantía de pago.",
    "answer": "guarantee, assurance",
    "answerDetails": "The bank holds the title to the car as a guarantee of payment."
  },
  {
    "id": 4461,
    "question": "ruedas",
    "questionDetails": "Salvo que no tenía ruedas.",
    "answer": "wheels, casters, wheeled",
    "answerDetails": "Except it didn’t have any wheels."
  },
  {
    "id": 4462,
    "question": "interrogatorio",
    "questionDetails": "Todo este interrogatorio es irrelevante.",
    "answer": "questioning",
    "answerDetails": "This whole line of questioning is irrelevant."
  },
  {
    "id": 4463,
    "question": "cuales",
    "questionDetails": "Ninguno de los cuales pueden ser ignorados.",
    "answer": "which",
    "answerDetails": "None of which can be ignored."
  },
  {
    "id": 4464,
    "question": "batería",
    "questionDetails": "Penélope toca la batería en una banda de rock.",
    "answer": "drums, battery",
    "answerDetails": "Penelope plays drums in a rock band."
  },
  {
    "id": 4465,
    "question": "insisto",
    "questionDetails": "Yo siempre insisto en comprar el primero.",
    "answer": "insist",
    "answerDetails": "I always insist on buying the first one."
  },
  {
    "id": 4466,
    "question": "logra",
    "answer": "Achieved"
  },
  {
    "id": 4467,
    "question": "vinieras",
    "questionDetails": "Te dije que no vinieras aqui.",
    "answer": "come",
    "answerDetails": "I told you not to come here."
  },
  {
    "id": 4468,
    "question": "unión",
    "questionDetails": "La Unión de estas tuberías está rota.",
    "answer": "union",
    "answerDetails": "The Pipe Union is broken."
  },
  {
    "id": 4469,
    "question": "devuelvo",
    "questionDetails": "Te devuelvo tus zapatos.",
    "answer": "return",
    "answerDetails": "I return you your shoes."
  },
  {
    "id": 4470,
    "question": "hueso",
    "questionDetails": "Suministran jamones de la manera tradicional, en el hueso.",
    "answer": "bone",
    "answerDetails": "They supply hams in the traditional way, on the bone."
  },
  {
    "id": 4471,
    "question": "enviado",
    "questionDetails": "Mandaré un enviado especial que.",
    "answer": "envoy",
    "answerDetails": "I will send a special envoy who."
  },
  {
    "id": 4472,
    "question": "menudo",
    "answer": "small"
  },
  {
    "id": 4473,
    "question": "gustos",
    "questionDetails": "Empecemos por tus gustos y aversiones.",
    "answer": "likes",
    "answerDetails": "Let’s start with your likes and dislikes."
  },
  {
    "id": 4474,
    "question": "grites",
    "questionDetails": "No grites, está cerrado.",
    "answer": "shout, yell, scream",
    "answerDetails": "You do not shout, is closed."
  },
  {
    "id": 4475,
    "question": "llamarlo",
    "answer": "call him"
  },
  {
    "id": 4476,
    "question": "recuerden",
    "questionDetails": "Y recuerden que creemos en el sistema del honor.",
    "answer": "remember, remind",
    "answerDetails": "And remember, we believe in the honour system."
  },
  {
    "id": 4477,
    "question": "golpeó",
    "questionDetails": "La madre de Miguel le gritó cuando golpeó a su hermanita.",
    "answer": "he hit",
    "answerDetails": "Miguel’s mother yelled at him when he hit his little sister."
  },
  {
    "id": 4478,
    "question": "queja",
    "questionDetails": "Tener motivos de queja.",
    "answer": "complaint, grievance",
    "answerDetails": "To have cause or grounds for complaint."
  },
  {
    "id": 4479,
    "question": "termines",
    "questionDetails": "A tu hermano le importa que termines tu tarea.",
    "answer": "finish",
    "answerDetails": "Your brother cares if you finish your homework."
  },
  {
    "id": 4480,
    "question": "acercarse",
    "questionDetails": "Repito, no deben acercarse a él.",
    "answer": "approach",
    "answerDetails": "I repeat, you must not approach him."
  },
  {
    "id": 4481,
    "question": "hicieras",
    "questionDetails": "Te dijo que no hicieras nada.",
    "answer": "do",
    "answerDetails": "He told you to do nothing."
  },
  {
    "id": 4482,
    "question": "firmó",
    "questionDetails": "Y te la firmó.",
    "answer": "signed",
    "answerDetails": "And he signed it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4483,
    "question": "perdamos",
    "questionDetails": "Si no perdamos más tiempo.",
    "answer": "lose",
    "answerDetails": "If we don’t lose anymore time."
  },
  {
    "id": 4484,
    "question": "bandera",
    "questionDetails": "La bandera del Parlamento ondeaba a media asta.",
    "answer": "flag, banner",
    "answerDetails": "The flag on the parliament building was flying at half mast."
  },
  {
    "id": 4485,
    "question": "pegarle",
    "answer": "Hit"
  },
  {
    "id": 4486,
    "question": "garganta",
    "questionDetails": "Escocia tomó el juego por la garganta.",
    "answer": "throat, gorge",
    "answerDetails": "Scotland took the game by the throat."
  },
  {
    "id": 4487,
    "question": "explicas",
    "questionDetails": "Cómo tú explicas esa forma.",
    "answer": "explain",
    "answerDetails": "How do you explain this?"
  },
  {
    "id": 4488,
    "question": "llevaban",
    "questionDetails": "Llevaban el uniforme en la marcha y se metieron en líos por eso.",
    "answer": "they wore",
    "answerDetails": "They wore the uniform to the March and got in trouble for it."
  },
  {
    "id": 4489,
    "question": "miseria",
    "questionDetails": "Mis padres perdieron sus trabajos y vivimos en miseria unos años.",
    "answer": "misery, poverty, squalor",
    "answerDetails": "My parents lost their jobs and we lived in misery for a few years."
  },
  {
    "id": 4490,
    "question": "soñado",
    "answer": "Dreamed"
  },
  {
    "id": 4491,
    "question": "sientan",
    "questionDetails": "Sientan el peso de esa mochila.",
    "answer": "feel",
    "answerDetails": "Feel the weight of that bag."
  },
  {
    "id": 4492,
    "question": "reconocido",
    "questionDetails": "El curso que voy a tomar está reconocido internacionalmente.",
    "answer": "recognised",
    "answerDetails": "The course I’ll be taking is internationally recognised."
  },
  {
    "id": 4493,
    "question": "rápidamente",
    "questionDetails": "La ciudad está creciendo rápidamente.",
    "answer": "quickly, rapidly, fast",
    "answerDetails": "The city is growing quickly."
  },
  {
    "id": 4494,
    "question": "intervención",
    "questionDetails": "La intervención del profesor en la discusión nos ayudó a llegar a un acuerdo.",
    "answer": "contribution, intervention",
    "answerDetails": "The professor’s contribution to the discussion helped us come to an agreement."
  },
  {
    "id": 4495,
    "question": "afectado",
    "questionDetails": "Usted podría llegar a ser diferente afectado hacia él.",
    "answer": "affected",
    "answerDetails": "You might become differently affected towards him."
  },
  {
    "id": 4496,
    "question": "moverse",
    "questionDetails": "Ninguno de los lados quería moverse.",
    "answer": "budge",
    "answerDetails": "Neither side would budge."
  },
  {
    "id": 4497,
    "question": "necesitábamos",
    "answer": "Needed"
  },
  {
    "id": 4498,
    "question": "tiré",
    "questionDetails": "… a mi habitación y me tiré de rodillas.",
    "answer": "threw myself, threw, banged",
    "answerDetails": "… to my room and threw myself on my knees."
  },
  {
    "id": 4499,
    "question": "fumando",
    "questionDetails": "Esos hombres están fumando.",
    "answer": "smoking, smokin’, puffing",
    "answerDetails": "Those men over there are smoking."
  },
  {
    "id": 4500,
    "question": "javier",
    "questionDetails": "Javier asó langosta a la parrilla para su mamá en el Día de la Madre.",
    "answer": "xavier",
    "answerDetails": "Xavier grilled some lobster for his mother on Mother’s Day."
  }
]